thepassiontest.com 2019-08-10

# Privacy Statement | ThePassionTest.com

You are here: [Home](https://thepassiontest.com/ "ThePassionTest.com") / Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement

Enlightened Alliances has created this privacy statement with respect to our websites in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our websites, www.thepassiontest.com, www.janetattwood.com, www.enlightenedalliances.com, www.mypassiontest.com, www.enlightenedbesteller.com, www.thehiddenriches.com.

We DO NOT sell, rent or give your name or contact information to third parties without your permission. When you purchase a product or product package which is provided in part or wholly by a third party, we will provide your contact information to those parties so they may provide the products and/or services you have purchased. We consider your payment for such products or product packages your permission to share your contact information with such parties.

Our site, from time to time, may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Our site’s registration form(s) may require(s) you to give us contact information (like your name and email address), unique identifiers, and optional information (like your mailing address) when you request products or services from us. Your contact information is used to contact you when necessary, such as sending opted-in promotional material. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; or emails.

Unique identifiers (such as user names and passwords) are collected for use as account numbers in our record system. Profile data is also sometimes collected at our site. We use this data to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content according to your preferences.

This site, may from time to time, contain links to other sites. Enlightened Alliances is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### Public Forums

This site, from time to time, may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. We have provided the user with the capability to select a username to protect their privacy on the public message boards.

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

Scroll to top
